

SHAIK SADIQ

Graphic Designer

My Contact

shaiksadiq621@gmail.com

() +91 8520994934

Tarnaka (secunderabad)

Portfolio Link

Hard Skill

- photoshop
- Illustrator
- Adobe XD
- Figma,
- CANVA
- Sketch
- AFTER EFFECTS

Soft Skill

- Observation
- · Decision making
- Communication
- Multi-tasking

Language

- English
- Hindi
- Telugu

About Me

I am a graphic designer. I will create icons and social media posts. I design eye-catching and creative posts for social media, as well as original icons for websites, apps, labels, and most other icons, which I can create easily. Additionally, I have experience designing quality graphics and Visualizing design.

Education Background

2018 - 2022 JNTUH University

BACHELORS OF TECHNOLOGY

Sana Engineering College Kodad (Suryapet Dist)

2015 - 2018 SBTET UNIVERSITY

POLYTECHNIC

Ses Sn Murthy Polytechnic College (Khammam Dist)

2005 - 2015 Higher Education Secondary Telangana

SCHOOLING

Zphs Government High School

Professional Experience

2022 – 2023 Worked in inlife Pharma as Graphic design specialist

2023 - 2024 Worked in The Go-To-Guy Agency as

Creative Graphic designer

Declaration

I hereby declare that all the information given above is true to that best of my knowledge and belief.